// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q026: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Dr. Tsai has been invited as a keynote ------ at the upcoming Mechanical Engineering Conference.',
      choices: ['spoken', 'speakers', 'speaker', 'speaking'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['speaker'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題251-260/#q251',
    },
    {
      question: 'One of the items you ordered is currently out of ------ and will be shipped as soon as it is received.',
      choices: ['order', 'service', 'shape', 'stock'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['stock'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題251-260/#q252',
    },
    {
      question: 'The extension of the term of the Chairman of the Recycling Promotion Committee was approved ------.',
      choices: ['keenly', 'unanimously', 'relatively', 'considerably'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['unanimously'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題251-260/#q253',
    },
    {
      question: 'Directions for replacing parts of the printer ------ in the attached operation manual.',
      choices: ['have included', 'include', 'are including', 'are included'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['are included'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題251-260/#q254',
    },
    {
      question: '------ the accounting and human resources departments are located on the second floor of the main office.',
      choices: ['Both', 'Neither', 'Not only', 'Either'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Both'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題251-260/#q255',
    },
    {
      question: 'The number of visitors to yesterday’s charity concert rose by ------ 20% compared to last year.',
      choices: ['vaguely', 'accordingly', 'nearly', 'strongly'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['nearly'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題251-260/#q256',
    },
    {
      question: 'Considering Ms. Peters’ excellent accomplishments, she is one of the most ------ candidates in next month’s election for mayor.',
      choices: ['multiple', 'evident', 'accurate', 'promising'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['promising'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題251-260/#q257',
    },
    {
      question: 'The new inexpensive material developed by Copley Tech is highly ------ to stains.',
      choices: ['resisted', 'resistant', 'resistance', 'resist'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['resistant'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題251-260/#q258',
    },
    {
      question: 'The welcome party for Ms. Costa ------ next Friday after work in the conference room on the second floor.',
      choices: ['was held', 'holds', 'will hold', 'will be held'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['will be held'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題251-260/#q259',
    },
    {
      question: 'The latest version of the long-awaited accounting software will ------ be released tomorrow.',
      choices: ['finalize', 'finally', 'final', 'finalizing'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['finally'],
      score: 1,
      commentUrl: 'https://get-toeic.com/toeic-part5-練習問題251-260/#q260',
    },
  ],
}